http://www.indianvedicastrology.com/content/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy | Indian Vedic Astrology
Skip to main content
Indian Vedic Astrology
Astrology consulting since 2002.
Home
Privacy Policy
IndianVedicAstrology.com is part of VMC Infotech, owned and run by Vikkramm Chandirramani. This privacy policy describes how we collect, use, and share personally identifiable information (information that can be used to identify you, such as your full name, email address, mailing address, or telephone number) ("PII") we obtain from and about individuals irrespective of their geographical location, both online and off-line.
IndianVedicAstrology.com is a website for general audiences and we do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13 years of age.
This policy may be modified from time to time to reflect industry initiatives or changes in the law, our information collection and use practices, the features of our websites, or technology. If we make revisions that change the way we collect or use your PII, those changes will be posted in this Policy. Therefore, you should review it periodically so that you are up to date on our most current policies and practices. If we materially change our practices regarding use of your PII, your PII will continue to be governed by the policy under which it was collected unless you have been provided notice of, and have not objected to, the change.
COLLECTION: Collection of PII by VMC Infotech
General. VMC Infotech collects PII in order to create or enhance our relationship with you. When we collect PII from you it is because you are voluntarily submitting the information to us in order to consult us for Astrology, numerology and other advice based on forecasting and predicting methods.
Cookies. Cookies are small bits of information that are placed on the hard drive of your computer when you visit the VMC Infotech Sites. We may use cookies to recognize users who have already registered for a VMC Infotech website, allowing those users to speed up their future activities on the VMC Infotech Sites. Information about your activities on VMC Infotech sites and other non-personally identifiable information about you may also be used to tailor the online ads you encounter to those we believe are consistent with your interests.
Third party advertisements displayed on the VMC Infotech web Sites may also contain cookies set by Internet advertising companies or advertisers. VMC Infotech does not control these cookies. You should check the privacy policy of the Internet advertising company or advertiser to see whether and how it uses cookies. See the "Notice" section below for more information on third party advertisements.
* Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to your website.* Google's use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads when you visit our site and/or other sites on the Internet.* You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the advertising opt-out page. Alternatively, you can opt out of a third-party vendor's use of cookies by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page.)
VMC Infotech may use cookies and similar tools to relate your use of the VMC Infotech Sites to PII obtained from you or a third party. For example, if you've asked us to provide you with information about our products or promotions, cookie and/or click stream data about your activities on the VMC Infotech Sites may allow us to limit the materials we provide you to items we think you will find interesting, based on your prior online activities and preferences.
You can set your computer to alert you each time a cookie is being sent or to refuse cookies completely. However, without cookies, you may not have access to certain features on the VMC Infotech Sites.
Web beacons. The VMC Infotech Sites may contain electronic images known as Web beacons - sometimes called single-pixel gifs - that may be used to assist in delivering or accessing cookies on our sites and allow us to count users who have visited those pages and to deliver co-branded services. We may include Web beacons in promotional e-mail messages or our newsletters in order to determine whether messages have been opened and acted upon.
We may also employ Web beacons from third parties in order to help us compile aggregated statistics and determine the effectiveness of our promotional campaigns. We prohibit Web beacons on our sites from being used by third parties to collect or access your personal information.
We may work with other companies that advertise on the VMC Infotech Sites to place Web beacons on their sites in order to allow us to develop statistics on how often clicking on an advertisement on an VMC Infotech site results in a purchase or other action on the advertiser's site.
NOTICE: VMC Infotech Will Provide You with Notice About its PII Collection Practices
When you voluntarily provide PII in response to our request or we authorize a third party to collect PII from you on the VMC Infotech web sites, we will inform you about who is collecting the information, how and why the information is being collected, and the types of uses VMC Infotech will make of the information At the time you provide your PII, VMC Infotech will notify you of your options regarding our use of your PII (See "Choice" below). This Policy describes the types of other companies that may want to send you information about their products and services and with whom we may want to share your personal information, as provided in this Policy (See "Use" below).
Sometimes we collect PII from consumers in manual format or off-line, such as a post card or subscription form. Providing detailed notice in those situations often proves impractical, so consumers will instead be provided with a short notice that describes how to obtain the full text of this Policy and other relevant information from us.
When you sign up with our partners for services such as userpages, and other services, you are providing information to the partner offering the service as well as to VMC Infotech. Use of your PII by the partner is subject to that partner's privacy policy, and you should carefully read the privacy policy of the partner providing the service before deciding to take advantage of the service.
The VMC Infotech Sites may be linked to Internet sites operated by other companies. Some of these third party sites may be co-branded with a VMC Infotech or affiliated entity's logo, even though they are not operated or maintained by VMC Infotech. The VMC Infotech Sites also carry advertisements from other companies. VMC Infotech is not responsible for the privacy practices of web sites operated by third parties that are linked to the VMC Infotech Sites or for the privacy practices of third party or national Internet advertising companies. Once you've left an VMC Infotech Site via such a link or by clicking on an advertisement, you should check the applicable privacy policy of the third party or advertiser site to determine how they will handle any PII they collect from you.
The VMC Infotech Sites may also be linked to sites operated by companies affiliated with VMC Infotech. Visitors to those affiliated sites should refer to their separate privacy policies and practices, which may differ in some respects from this Policy.
Some of the advertisements that appear on the VMC Infotech Sites are delivered to you by national Internet advertising companies such as those listed below. These companies utilize certain technologies to deliver advertisements and marketing messages and to collect anonymous information about your visit to the VMC Infotech Sites, including information about the ads they display, via a cookie placed on your computer that reads (or approximates) your IP address.
CHOICE: VMC Infotech Will Provide You with Choices About the Use of Your PII
VMC Infotech will not use your PII for purposes different from those about which you have been notified, or share your PII with third parties that are not affiliated with VMC Infotech, unless you have asked to receive certain information and/or services from third parties or participate in certain third-party programs and have been notified that the fulfillment of such a request requires the sharing of your PII or you have consented to such sharing.
USE: VMC Infotech's Use of PII
VMC Infotech will use your PII in a manner that is consistent with this Policy. If VMC Infotech obtains PII from a third party, such as a business partner, our use of that information is governed by this Policy. VMC Infotech may use PII in aggregate, anonymous form for research purposes.
We may contact you regarding account status, changes to this Policy, our User Agreement or other terms of use, to confirm your registration, for customer service purposes or for any other business reason related to your use of VMC Infotech Sites.
We will never share your credit card information with third parties except those VMC Infotech uses to perform tasks (such as order fulfillment and payment processing) required to complete purchases you make through web sites.
VMC Infotech employees, agents, and contractors are required to have a legitimate business reason to obtain access to your PII.
VMC Infotech may also enter into agreements with outside companies that possess the technology that allows VMC Infotech to customize the advertising and marketing messages you receive on the VMC Infotech Sites.VMC Infotech automatically updates software used in conjunction with certain of the services available on the VMC Infotech Sites. In order to accomplish this, VMC Infotech collects information about a user's current version of the software from the user's computer. This information is not archived but is only used to determine which software requires updating.
There may be instances when VMC Infotech may disclose PII without providing you with a choice in order to protect the legal rights of VMC Infotech, their employees, agents, and contractors; to protect the safety and security of visitors to our web sites; to investigate, prevent or protect against suspected fraud, illegal activity, violations of our user agreement or for risk management purposes; or to respond to summons, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims. In addition, if VMC Infotech sells all or part of its business or makes a sale or transfer of assets or is otherwise involved in a merger or business transfer, VMC Infotech may transfer your PII to a third party as part of that transaction.
SECURITY: VMC Infotech Protects the Security of PII
VMC Infotech uses reasonable administrative, technical, personnel, and physical measures to safeguard PII in its possession against loss, theft and unauthorized use, disclosure, or modification. Passwords and other sensitive information stored by VMC Infotech are encrypted in transit.
Notwithstanding these security measures, please be aware that when you submit PII to the VMC Infotech Sites over the Internet, the information may travel over many systems that are not under the VMC Infotech's control and may not be secure.
If a password is used to help protect your accounts and personal information, it is your responsibility to keep your password confidential. Do not share this information with anyone. Anyone who has access to your password will have access to your PII, as well as to any credit card information that you have submitted. If you are sharing a computer with anyone you should always log out before leaving a site or service to protect access to your information from subsequent users.
ACCESS: How to Access, Correct, or Delete Your Preferences Regarding Your PII
To access, correct or update your account or other Personal Information such as your city or interests, please use the "My Account" link on the VMC Infotech Site on which you are registered.
If you want to update your email address or stop receiving these types of promotional emails, please follow the procedures to unsubscribe at the bottom of any email we send you. You may unsubscribe from any Premium service for which you have previously elected by following the instructions included in the VMC Infotech User Agreement.
REMEDIES AND COMPLIANCE: How to Contact VMC Infotech About Privacy Concerns
If you have any other questions, comments or complaints about this Policy, please contact us via our online form or write to us at:
VMC InfotechAttn: Legal Department/Privacy Administrator222/ Shantivan,New Link Rx. Extn.,Andheri westMumbai 53India
Get in touch | Privacy Policy | Disclaimer | Copyright 2002-2020 VMC Infotech, All rights reserved.
Clickbank
"ClickBank is the retailer of products on this site. CLICKBANK® is a registered trademark of Click Sales, Inc., a Delaware corporation located at 1444 S. Entertainment Ave., Suite 410 Boise, ID 83709, USA and used by permission. ClickBank's role as retailer does not constitute an endorsement, approval or review of these products or any claim, statement or opinion used in promotion of these products."
